<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoGoGatchi</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="register">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="login">Log-In</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="upload_profile_pic"> Upload Picture</string>
    <string name="update_profile_settings"> Update Profile Settings</string>
    <string name="update_companion_settings"> Update Companion Settings</string>
    <string name="interests">Interests-</string>
    <string name="amusement_park">Amusement Park</string>
    <string name="art_gallery">Art Gallery</string>
    <string name="bar">Bar</string>
    <string name="cafe">Cafe</string>
    <string name="campground">Campground</string>
    <string name="lodging">Lodging</string>
    <string name="movie_theatre">Movie Theatre</string>
    <string name="night_club">Night Club</string>
    <string name="park">Park</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="shopping_mall">Shopping Mall</string>
    <string name="stadium">Stadium</string>
    <string name="travel_agency">Travel Agency</string>
    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="zoo">Zoo</string>
    <string name="location">Allow Location Access</string>
    <string name="notifications">Allow Push Notifications</string>
    <string name="distance">Select Distance to Search</string>
    <string name="miles">miles</string>
    <string name="reviews">See Reviews</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="menu_icon">menu_icon</string>
    <string name="news"> news_icon</string>
    <string name="title_activity_monster_hatch">MonsterHatchActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="companion">[Insert quirky location facts here]</string>
    <string name="no_idea">Looks like we\'re out of ideas. Please tap here to refresh.</string>
    <string name="call_location">Call</string>
    <string name="companionFarm">Companion</string>

    <string name="profile">profile</string>
    <string name="locationView">Location Details</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="newsFeed">Feed</string>
    <string name="profileLarge">Profile</string>

    <string name="register2">Register</string>
    <string name="optional">Optional</string>
    <string name="display_name">Display Name</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="passwordHint">Password (min. 6 char)</string>
    <string name="passwordHintCheck">Re-Enter Password</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="checkEmail">Re-Enter Email</string>

    <string name="termsConditions">Privacy</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo1">TODO1</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="visit_website">Visit Website</string>

    <string name="TermsAndConditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="TermsText">Terms of Service ("Terms")
==========================

Last updated: August 12, 2018

Please read these Terms of Service ("Terms", "Terms of Service") carefully
before using the http://www.GoGoGatchi.com website (the "Service") operated by
GoGoGatchi ("us", "we", or "our").

Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and
compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and
others who access or use the Service.

By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you
disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service. This
Terms of Service agreement for GoGoGatchi is [based on the Terms and
Conditions from TermsFeed](https://termsfeed.com/terms-conditions/generator/).

Accounts
--------

When you create an account with us, you must provide us information that is
accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a
breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your account
on our Service.

You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the
Service and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your
password is with our Service or a third-party service.

You agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us
immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use
of your account.

Links To Other Web Sites
------------------------

Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are
not owned or controlled by GoGoGatchi.

GoGoGatchi has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the
content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or
services. You further acknowledge and agree that GoGoGatchi shall not be
responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused
or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any
such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or
services.

We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies
of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.

Termination
-----------

We may terminate or suspend access to our Service immediately, without prior
notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation
if you breach the Terms.

All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive termination
shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership
provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.

We may terminate or suspend your account immediately, without prior notice or
liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you
breach the Terms.

Upon termination, your right to use the Service will immediately cease. If you
wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service.

All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive termination
shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership
provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.

Governing Law
-------------

These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of
California, United States, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be
considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held
to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these
Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement
between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior
agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.

Changes
-------

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms
at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 days
notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material
change will be determined at our sole discretion.

By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become
effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to
the new terms, please stop using the Service.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.

</string>

    <string name="privacyText">Privacy Policy
Effective date: August 12, 2018

GoGoGatchi ("us", "we", or "our") operates the website and the GoGoGatchi mobile application (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. This Privacy Policy for GoGoGatchi is powered by FreePrivacyPolicy.com.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

Email address
First name and last name
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data").

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer\'s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

Tracking &amp; Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
GoGoGatchi uses the collected data for various purposes:

To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

GoGoGatchi will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
GoGoGatchi may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of GoGoGatchi
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy &amp; Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en

Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

By email: proDevs@GoGoGatchi.com
By visiting this page on our website: http://www.GoGoGatchi.com</string>

    <string name="privacyDataTitle">Privacy/Data</string>


    <!--- gender drop list-->
    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Select Option..</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--- ethnicity drop list-->
    <string-array name="interest">
        <item>Select Option..</item>
        <item>Athletics</item>
        <item>Cultural</item>
        <item>Monuments</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--- age drop list-->
    <string-array name="age">
        <item>Select Option..</item>
        <item>Below 18</item>
        <item>18–24</item>
        <item>25–34</item>
        <item>35–44</item>
        <item>45–54</item>
        <item>65 or more</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
